Hello everyone!
So, it's been a while since I've had an EcoLove moto!
Yay!
It's been a long time! Today, I'm here again at Hamanaka, the boat race that you all know and love, and today, I'll be talking about the
Today is the first day of the 8th round of the Venus Series, the Monthly Boat Race Cup. Today is the first day of the 8th race of the Venus Series, the Monthly Boat Race Cup. What do you think?
Oh, it's good, isn't it?
We are going to start with race 5,
First of all, I would like to welcome today's guests.
These two are with us today. Please come in!
Please give them my best regards.
Yay!
Please have a seat.
Excuse me. Thank you very much.
Yes, let me introduce myself.
I'm Yori Noguchi from Equal Love.
Yanazukun, this is Risa Otoshima from Equal Love.
Yay!
That's great!
I'm glad that two of you are here.
This is your first time at Riso.
It's my first time, and I'm glad to have a girl from Hama here.
It's pretty much my first time here and I really don't know what to expect.
But I hope we can have fun while doing it!
Let's have fun!
I'm sure everyone will be a little confused at first, so don't worry about it!
Just have fun!
This is Iori's second time.
It was live, right?
That's right!
It's your first video, right?
It's been a while since the first one.
I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you for coming.
Good night.
I'm the Boat Race Hamanaka Ladies Festival promotion committee member.
I've just finished the inaugural event, and I've just come home.
I still have a seat available here today.
We have a former boat racer, Ms. Yuka Takahashi here again today!
Thank you very much!
Ms. Takahashi
My master
Master
Those of you who are former rei
If you are a former active person or something, if you don't know anything
Please ask a real beginner
Teacher, please.
Because all of us are out more than these members.
Please join us today.
Please.
Now, if I could explain today...
We're going to forecast for three races today.
So each of you has a budget of 10,000 yen.
But how you spend that 10,000 yen in the three races is up to you.
And here in Shizuoka Prefecture...
If you get a good refund today...
I'm going to a certain hamburger steak restaurant!
That... that...
A very refreshing looking hamburger steak shop!
A hamburger joint that looks so refreshing.
Maybe we can all go there together.
So let's work hard today.
I want to try it.
Let's all be fresh.
Let's be fresh!
Can I ask you a question?
I'm going to be working as an ambassador for the Ladies' Sens.
I will be working for the PG-1 Speed Queen Memorial to be held in February next year.
What kind of race is this?
The PG-1 Speed Queen Memorial is a newly established event.
That's right.
It's a big race for women.
The big race.
The first edition of the memorial will be
will be held at Lake Hamana in February next year in 2025.
The duration of the race for the competitors is
Until the 30th of November this year.
In that time, the fastest time of the race
The fastest time in the race will be the first one to be selected.
It's a novel idea.
Anyway, it will be decided by the fastest time.
The fastest time in the race will be chosen from the 24
The fastest ones are gathered
The big race will be held
The excitement distribution of it
Raise the excitement
Excitement
It's a real charade!
I'd like to make a prediction as soon as possible.
I'd like to make a prediction about the 4th store of the race.
I'm a friend of a player named Momoi Kawaii and a grandmother who did the voice of a woman.
I call her Momoi-chan because of her voice, and we are good friends.
We're good friends, so I wanted to cheer for Momoi-chan in the five races, and I wanted to cheer for the athletes I wanted to cheer for.
It might be easier if you make a list. I see. Is there anyone you're interested in?
For example, Mizumi Fukuoka of the No. 1 series. She's the first winner of each race.
Winner? Winner! Wow! It's the first time she won the championship.
What series are you in? Series 4. Is it here?
Great. This time?
No. 1, No. 1. Oh, I wonder if he'll come.
But Watanabe here, on course 2, has a good grip, so if he attacks, Yamakawa-san will be right next to him, so...
So if you attack, if you have Yamakawa-san, who is a solid dancer, next to you, so if 2 comes, 2 will grip and 1 will be surprised, and then 3 will stab him with a big swing.
Then Momoi can come, too Momoi can develop, too
I think my Hosokawa is colored, but he's A1, so he's the highest ranked player
A1, A2, B1, B2...
Start display
How do you see this?
You're late for the start, aren't you?
Momoi is here.
The motors this time.
Among these, the one with the best power selection is No. 1, Fukuoka Izu.
What? What should we do?
What are you going to do?
Momoi, your engine is colored, too.
Momo-i-chan?
I've got a good feeling about 1 and 4 having engine color.
I have faith in you, Momoi.
The power of faith.
Because we did it... together.
What kind of strategy did you have in mind earlier?
Today's strategy?
It's meta, but it's my birthday number, so I want to put 246 in.
I'll definitely put in 246 every time. Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely. Can I put it on? 246 is 56, so it's an eagle box.
I have an Iori box that has taken over this club and helped us all many times. What's in it for you, Risa? I don't have one.
You don't have one. But Risa has a light blue one, so she has an Ambote.
I think black is cool!
I like that it's blue.
I like that.
And red, too.
Yes, it is.
The eyes...
Yeah, they do.
That one looks strong, too.
The bouncing sub-contact looks strong.
I wonder if it's strong.
I have a gut feeling.
And sometimes my instincts are right.
Maybe it's better not to think about it too much.
Maybe... the more I think about it, the more I think about it.
The more I think about it, the more I think about it.
I don't know, the more I think about it, the more I don't know.
3-3
There it is! Here it is!
3-3 predicted!
1-2-3-6, 2-3-4-6, 3-1-2-4-6.
The second boat is still what to do here.
And the 3 boats will depend on it.
If the second boat comes to the finish, the third boat will either roll around or go straight to the finish.
If 2 comes to the finish, 3 will have no choice but to roll up or roll up to the finish.
1 is more likely to run away, but if 2 runs away, the 3 horses are sold.
I think I'll fix Momoe.
Fix Momoe? Axis?
You're right. We'll put an axis lip on it.
What's that called?
I don't know.
Izumi Takagawa, the first boat, is not usually that good in the data.
She seems to lose both by getting stabbed and by getting caught in the middle.
This is getting interesting.
Oh, man, this takes a lot of brain power.
But it's a good engine.
Yes, it is.
And it's showing.
I'm not surprised he's running away.
He's got a good engine. He's in Hamamatsu. He's wide open.
As long as he gets a good start and goes around first...
as long as he goes around first, he can take advantage of his engine's legs
There's a good chance he'll be able to make it through.
I'll be at Hamanaka again.
I think the day may have come for me to repeat the Zen-mo-Zen thing I did the other day in Hamanaka.
Like Zen to Zen too.
Yeah.
Zen zen zen momo.
How many ways is it zen zen momo?
I don't think.
I thought it.
Twenty ways.
Twenty, right?
I'm the lady of the house.
I've heard so many words come out of your mouth.
I don't remember any of them.
I'm 123, 123, 6 for these 6 points, by the way.
Hosokawa-san is so good on the road.
Oh, man!
I'm sure he'll come up to the tripod with a fixed surface.
123, 123
Mr. Takai-san hit a one-shoe in the off-screen race just now.
He's in great shape today.
Mr. Hosokawa already trusts his skills.
I haven't had money on youtube in a while.
I miss this place! I can't see here.
I heard this is how you did it.
Like this one?
I miss it.
I'm sorry, I don't even know how to buy.
You have to put some money in the machine. - How?
How?
Please put some money in!
Lisa's buying for the first time.
Put your bus card in.
Put this in here.
Is it the right way around?
Are you okay?
This way?
No, no, no, sorry, sorry.
Then it's ready to issue.
You can press the issue button, too.
I need a bus card.
Okay, I got it.
It's like the first time I'm running an errand.
I got it.
Like it's your first time shopping.
What?
Well, well, well, well.
Well, well, well, well
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Now then, I'll go first.
There you go!
I bought 13 or so.
This time, I didn't buy any at all.
I would have been fine with peaches, but peaches would have cost too much, so I'll go with the 13,000 yen peaches with your advice, Mr. Takahashi. Please do!
Then, from next time, I bought a box of 136, and another box of 246.
I was told to follow the reporter's advice.
Maybe for the first time, or that type.
I believe the reporter, so I'm really asking for your help.
Great, lots of them.
136, 134, 316, 314, 213.
Isn't that the most decent one?
All of them.
I said, "That's right, that's right, that's what the reporter predicted...
Here we go.
It's true.
Yes, it's true.
I'm nervous. It's been a long time since I've been to a boat race.
Oh, man!
Cool!
I'm ready.
Everybody
I'm scared
Oh, the new name has changed, but it's here.
What do you mean?
It's 1, 2, 3, 6, 4, 5...
Mr. Fukuyama is on the fourth course.
What do you mean?
Oh my God, it's so easy to listen to rock music!
Oh, no, it's starting.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
One more time.
One more time!
Hang on, hang on, I have no idea
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there
Ugh! What?
Oh, it's pulling out.
Oh, my gosh.
Second place!
Go, go, go, go.
Second place, second place, second place.
Ride for second place!
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, there's second place.
Mr. Edd?
Come on, come on, come on.
Second place, second place.
Yummy, yummy.
Second place.
Great, great, great, great.
Here comes second place.
Delicious!
Second place!
Oh, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Huh?
Oh, no.
I don't know, I don't know.
Second place, then.
Huh? Lisango?
Second place?
Not risango?
Lisango!
Okay, but No. 6!
Where's 6th place?
Go for it!
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, sixth place!
Oh, wait, really?
Really?
Second place.
Cool.
Mr. No. 2, who's buying No. 6?
No, I'm not buying.
I'm in third place.
What happened to third place?
I ate in.
What? Wait a minute.
Okay, done!
Ah.
I was right.
What?
Did you guess right?
I was right.
Oh, that's funny.
Funny.
Weird.
Strange.
Uh, I see.
No, wait.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, wait a minute.
It was frustrating. Seriously, it was definitely race two, one, three, now.
Is that possible? How often does that happen?
But it's rare for Mr. Yamakawa to swing in like that, isn't it?
It was probably like he suddenly got on the deep end.
But even so, he still finished in fourth place, maybe in three races. That's amazing.
Let's switch over. There are only two races left.
By the way, do you remember the next race, Race 6?
Natsuki-chan is now. I do.
I have a video of her screaming all her life long ago.
How do you feel about the next race?
In the next race, too, this boat No. 1, Mr. Maniwa, is not so good at this race.
I'm so happy to see Mizuki Yamauchi in the 5th boat.
I've been chasing her since I was a little girl with my father.
Mizuki Yamauchi is a racer that my father and I have been chasing since I was a little girl, when I was just starting out.
When she was just starting out as a racer, she was featured in the Tavin, and I said, "Let's support her!
And now she's in this race with the boat racing team.
They are Meizuki and Mizuki...
Mizuki and Mizuki Zenki!
I'd like to win.
Isn't it going to be refreshing?
I want to be fresh!
Tsuchiya?
You're going to be in Dream today, right?
Yes, I will.
So Tsuchiya is popular and strong.
He's a local.
Local!
That's great!
So, for example... if Yin doesn't show up...
Do you think Emi is more likely to come?
I'm going to stick with two.
I'll do the same!
Alex?
Yes, yes! Why not?
You should do it!
The ace motorist with four wins and three championships.
I won last time with my motor, didn't I?
At Lake Biwa.
You won at Lake Biwa with a motor, didn't you?
I didn't know that was possible.
If you believe in Biwako Motor, you won.
Miyatama, 235 is the most popular so far
235, you know, Tsuchiya, Nazoki, Mizuki...
the most popular one!
I'm buying this! I'll buy it too.
I'll get on the train. Waiting for the train.
I like it. Here we go, Mr. Train.
Come on, Mr. Train. I'm waiting for the train.
Mizuki Eguchi said it was easy to ride, too.
Mizuki Natsuki said it was easy to ride.
Ito, the sixth store owner, also made a positive comment.
I'm really interested. And it's 6. I don't want to drag it out too much, but I'm so worried about the aesthetics.
Braille is out.
There's one.
What do you think of this?
Strawberry hands are easy to time because they don't have the same kind of pull.
So, I hope the second person in the group will do well.
Nonogi, the third one, has both colors, and her legs go around the circle.
I heard that Nonogi also has a color.
That's amazing.
What?
Based on that, I'll go with this.
Two, one, three, one, three, four, five.
With Misaki Tsuchiya's head fixed.
Natsumi Mania, 1.5 points, if Mania player turns first.
I'm thinking 2-1, leaving her to play.
And if she goes around, 3 points will be 2 and 3.
The third place will be fought over by 1, 3, 4, and 5.
I was curious about the S motor, but decided to cut it out.
I will copy your choice.
I thought that the third place would be quite crowded.
That's right.
Lisa?
Let's go, reporter.
What's that? There it is.
Oh, no! I was just about to imitate you, too, Natsuki.
Reporter.
Oh, no.
I knew you were a believer.
I'm listening, aren't I?
I'm listening to you, Mr. Reporter.
So did Mr. Takahashi.
Am I the only one who believes him?
It's a good motor.
Let's see how serious you are.
Absolutely.
Let's get him to show his true colors.
And I also heard that you got off to a good start.
That's why I'm hoping for a turn of events that even the press didn't see coming.
It could be a miracle.
That's right.
It's often the case that a newcomer like him draws a good engine and wins his first race.
If it comes, it's a big deal, so take the engine as your ally.
Race 6
Just Nodoka and Mizuki this time.
I changed it!
It's done! I put my heart and soul into it!
So, now that I've changed the lacraces
I'd like to present the clarification.
I'd like to introduce it in the ship's sword axis lip.
I'm going to start with Natsuki-chan's 3 axes.
And Mizuki is next.
3, 5, so it's Nadzuki-kizuki!
And Mizuki is next! And 2, 3, 5 and 2, 5, 3 are
2 on the axis of 2
2, Nazuki, Mizuki, 2, Mizuki, Nazuki
1, mizuki, mizuki.
I'll go this way this time.
Okay, four.
Okay, I'll take
I'll have two hands.
Two, three, five.
Two, three, four.
Two, four, five.
And, two, four, six boxes.
Thank you.
It's very one-chance, this time, isn't it?
I'm drawn to motors.
Speaking of being attracted to motors...
Then I'm attracted to motors.
I think you were a believer in reporters earlier.
Mr. Reporter didn't put six in the box, so...
I'm sure he'll run a race that betrays the development of Mr. Press.
I've got high hopes.
I'm sure you can do it while no one else is predicting it.
Certainly.
Third place is a six.
One, two, three, six.
That's good.
I wonder if the motor's coming.
Three, five, four.
If it comes, there's that one, there's that one.
I really wish you the best of luck.
Let's go.
Here we go, six races to go.
Good luck.
Go for it.
Here we go.
Come on. Come on.
I'm already so far behind.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Good luck.
Mizuki, you're late to the start.
That's the sixth time, right?
That's the sixth time.
Is the sixth one coming?
I don't know.
Six.
Is it bad?
Three.
Why is he coming?
Why are they coming?
Why are you here?
But Mizuki, too.
The third time.
Why are you here?
But...
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Come on!
Three, two, one.
No, no, no, no, no.
What's this?
It's Mr. Giraffe singing.
Mr. Giraffe!
Oh, no!
Oh, no! In the water!
The water!
Natsuki, you're number one!
Oh!
That's great!
The wave!
That's three in a row.
Who are they? You guessed it.
Why?
Congratulations, Nazki-chan!
That's great!
Good luck, Mizuki! I'm rooting for you!
Okay, we're done.
Let's go back.
It's the sleet one.
Mr. Press?
Wait, Mr. Press?
You hit it.
Oh, my God.
You should definitely come back next time.
You'll get it next time.
I'm so disappointed.
You did a great job.
That was great.
So, seven more races, and then the last one...
Don't be fresh.
I can't be fresh.
Then let's all be fresh together.
Yes, sir!
Liven it up!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Let's win for sure!
So, race seven.
How does it work?
He's in race 7?
Who's the same age as Mr. Harahashi?
Chika Maehara, the fifth place finisher.
Chika!
Chika Maehara.
Yes, in Okayama, right? Yes.
Okayama, same classmate.
Here's Yu Miura, who just gave flowers at the opening ceremonies.
Race 7, 3rd place
Tell me something.
Tell me.
By the way, in this race, too...
There's one who's not very good at the inside.
That's the kind of day it is today, isn't it?
That's the kind of program today.
That's the program.
Miyake, do you think you'll get one?
I'm sure of it.
A lot.
Is it possible?
No, no, Miyake.
Miyake?
Three, four, five.
I think it's going to sell pretty well. Three, four, five.
I think 3 and 4 are going to stay.
If number 1 gets off to a slow start, say, with a bang...
If the first one starts late, for example, the second one might be the first one to go out.
If the first one is late, for example, it is possible that the second one will start to roll out at the head of the line.
But in the end, 1 remains, doesn't it?
If we get ahead of them, we can stay in the race like we did in the last race.
But if we fall behind and get caught in the middle, we can't stay in the race.
Wait! Look at this!
All three horses, all popular, all otts!
Wow, really!
3, 4, 5, and the favorite! Oh no, it's Fingerprints!
It's Mr. Sashihara's race!
No, but really, Eri Miura is, let's say...
Are you listening?
Eri Miura is like Kashiwagi-san.
She's a veteran. She's like Spin-san to us.
She can be in any position, any song.
She says, "I can be in any position, any song, any word.
No matter the emotion.
That's why he's so popular.
Mr. Miura, are you good at what you do?
It's called the technical area.
Technical area
That's cool.
He's really flexible.
You really are Kashiwagi-san.
How is it going so far? What are our results?
What do you mean, how are we doing?
Not even now.
Too much.
Is it gone? Clean money?
Yeah, that's right, man. It's gone.
No one won anything.
That's not how the money came in.
Oh, my God.
Okay, then.
Two thousand three hundred and forty-five six.
3242456.
I'm completely off by one.
But I'm putting in the six.
You're up to six.
Makiko Yamaguchi
She was very tenacious on the way.
The wind was strong.
It was hard for everyone to ride.
I thought there was a possibility that she would pick up the pace if she came in third.
So, I'm putting her in the top 3.
But...
If there were two horses, Technical Ellie would already be in third place.
I'm sure Technical Ellie will come in.
If 2 is late, 2 will attack, and then 3 and 2 will stay in the pattern.
And if 3 and 2 are late together, 3 and 4.
If 3 and 2 are also late, 3 and 4.
If 3 and 2 lag behind, 3 and 4...
And if three and two are late together, three and four.
Three, if two are late together, three, four...
I'll look at the comments now... the first boat has hit the pella, but her hips and legs are not as good as they should be... but she's the third favorite... and they're all negative comments, aren't they, Mr. Reporter? Oh, there it is! Press? There's a four-feather ball, too? I believe you, Mr. Reporter. You're up to three in the first three.
Reporter?
You see this? The favorite has to be in the top 10. It's the favorite.
I have 300 yen left. Can I have it?
No, please, 200 yen.
Please, 200 yen.
Oh, no! It's great!
I've spent it all.
I really believe you, Mr. Press.
I figured out the last 100 yen on my own.
Mr. Star gave me the missing 200 yen.
I'm sure of it!
Then I'll announce it.
I'm 2323 all and 34345345
I was going to box.
But since it's just a minus on
Mr. Takahashi advised me to cut off the 5 at the head
From
Yes 246 birthday box
And Sanya-Rasan box
Sanya-Rasan box
321235324256
I wrote 345 here one more time.
Please do.
I'm totally disappointed in Kishida-san, so I betrayed him a while ago,
I should have kept on believing in him, so I'm going to give it one last try this time.
So, I'm going to give it a try for the last time, so here is Kishida-san's list of all the knock-knock styles.
Oh, really?
Really?
Yes, just as he said. Really, just as you said.
Three 1245.
Oh, Mr. Reporter.
I was going to cut it once, but I had 100 yen left over at the end.
I made the 2 that wasn't on either side of the head
I made 213.
Please, Mr. Press.
How many did you win in the last race?
Good luck!
Good luck in the last race.
Prayers all around.
We're always praying.
Please, please, please, please.
It's starting... it's starting...
Here it comes.
Please hang in there
I'll do my best.
Let's go!
Shut up!
Three, two, they're coming!
Two!
Please!
They're coming!
Wait, wait, wait, which one am I looking at? I don't remember.
I don't remember.
Wow, three!
Three!
Three, three, three, three, three, three, three, three, three, three!
Three, three, three, three, three, three, three, three!
There's one left.
Four is coming.
Come on!
What?
B, you're going to walk.
Oh, really? Kisha?
Come on!
Go, go, go, go, go! Go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Three, four.
But 3 already!
Three forty-five.
Oh, there you go.
ah, one and a half...
GOGOGO
Go 5!
5ike 5ike 5ike 5ike 5ike
5ike-5ike-5ike-5ike
I'm not going.
one by one
ichidatsu?
We'll go together...
Yay!
Oh, it's here! It's here!
It's here!
It's got to be here!
I'll only believe it if it comes!
Three, four, one!
Oh, my God!
Cool!
Risa's right! That's great!
But thanks to the reporter, not me.
No, you didn't.
But here's your refund.
It's me.
Let's go inside for a look.
What's this?
I don't know.
Oh, no.
The interest rate...
What the hell?
Risa-chan
Risa-chan, this.
You bought 200 yen, right? That means 1730 x 200, how much did you spend earlier? All of it.
All 4,600 yen.
Yes, Risa is Risa's explosion.
Well, come to this world. Come to this world.
Oh, Sakuwaku card. Or if you put in your vote.
Cool!
Yes!
Wait, I made a mistake. I looked at the wrong thing.
You can't see it.
That's amazing.
Yay!
That's the only refund I got today.
Board racing is fun.
So, three races are over.
Thank you very much.
Today's results, let's start with us, shall we?
Yes, sir.
What is it today?
I mean, nothing happened today.
Nothing.
Just two people losing 10,000 yen.
That's right.
No, no, no.
That was sad.
I'm sorry.
It was frustrating.
But it was so much fun.
I'm glad.
This is the last race.
Risai guessed it.
I wonder what it's like, the joy of winning, or maybe it's just that this kind of thing becomes a habit.
And Risa's recovery rate is 51.9%. It's totally negative.
Next? The end.
Absolutely! Absolutely! I can't let it end like this.
Please come back.
Please call me again.
How was it?
Well, I was happy that I guessed right in Race 5, but I was a little disappointed that everyone else didn't. Next time, let's all have a blast!
Next time, let's all have a blast together.
Next time, let's all have a blast. Please come again.
Trust me or the reporter.
Which is it?
Either one!
Thank you.
So that was Yuka Takahashi. Thank you very much.
See you again!
And last but not least, I have an announcement...
This is the one we are wearing right now.
The goods for the Equal Love Boat Race
It's a T-shirt for predicting the future of boat tickets.
You can see the badge on the back of the T-shirt.
We will be releasing a collaborative version with Boat Race Hamanaka.
A collaboration version will be released....
Here's a picture of it.
Here it is.
As you can see, Swacky Hamanaka's character Swacky is blue, so we made him a blue t-shirt.
The back side of the shirt is also designed for the collaboration.
You have to come here.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a photo of me with my panel, but I'm not here any more. I don't know either.
Yes, and as I said before, the panel I signed at the opening ceremony will be on display.
The panels that I signed at the opening ceremony will be on display at the museum, and they will change depending on the period of time.
Last but not least, Auto Race Hamanaka is running a "Follow & Repost" campaign.
Yes.
If you follow the official Auto Race Hamanaka x and repost the relevant post, you will be entered into a drawing for a chance to win a quo card autographed by us!
For more details, please see the summary column.
We will be holding a phone poll campaign during the g 3 All Ladies from August 19, 2012, where those who make a phone poll entry with a minimum purchase of 500 yen will be entered into a drawing to win our autographed goods and other prizes!
Please apply from the application form in the summary section.
Please check it out!
Please follow them to see the pit operation of the racers, event information, and so on.
That's all for today's Boat Race!
Will you come back again?
Sure! I'll do my best! Next time!
Let's all be fresh next time!
I promise!
I'll do my best!
I'm done. So, thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
I'll be at the moto race place.
I'm at the moto race place.
What, here?
It's so big!
It's so spacious.
There are so many seats!
Amazing!
Standing in this dungeon, I
I'm asking for your help.
I'm already nervous because it's such a big venue.
I'm sure everyone will be watching me warmly.
I will do my best and have fun.
Mr. Takahashi was with me.
We met in the elevator at the hotel this morning.
Mr. Takahashi!
We got along well together, so I'm sure we'll be fine.
If anything else happens, I'd like to leave it to you, Mr. Takahashi.
I'll do my best!
Yay! I'm an ambassador!
We'll be waiting for you.
We will first send a bouquet of flowers to Mr. Miura for his participation in the tournament.
Yes, good luck!
And thank you very much to Mr. Shibata!
He will appear again after the interview with the Dreamstay contestants.
Thank you very much.
Have a nice talk.
We will talk to you later.
And everyone!
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Miura was very kind.
I'm going to do it again!
Something like, oh, I'll do it!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm going to the inauguration ceremony next.
Oh, man...
Inauguration ceremony
I'll do my best once.
Good bye.
Thank you for your hard work.
I look forward to working with you.
Hamanaka Auto Race
Mr. Toshiyuki Suzuki, President of Suzuki Yukinami Corporation, will present the sashes.
Mr. Suzuki, I look forward to working with you.
Yes, sir.
Can you do it?
Please pass it through your hands.
Ah, yes.
Now let's take a commemorative photo.
Ladies and gentlemen of the press.
If you want to look at me again, just let me know.
Fans are welcome to have their pictures taken as well.
Please upload them on social networking sites and promote the event.
Thank you very much, Mr. Suzuki.
Please give us a lecture.
Thank you very much.
Your help suits you well.
You've been appointed as an ambassador for promotion.
How do you feel now?
I have never heard the name of an ambassador before, and to be honest, I'm surprised, but I'm very happy to be involved with Boat Race Hamanaka in this way.
I am very happy. I will do my best.
I will do my best. I am an ambassador of excitement, so I need to be excited about it.
Do you have any enthusiasm for the event?
Yes, I am. I am an ambassador to liven up the ladies' race,
I myself often go to watch and buy boats for the ladies' races,
I will do my best in that area.
I would like to do my best in that area. Then, I hope that you and the ladies will help me to make the race more exciting.
I would also like to introduce the East Rising Team panel.
We took pictures of you when you were inaugurated.
Wearing all six colors.
I borrowed Mr. Takai's helmet, etc., for the photo shoot.
Oh, isn't this a remote racer?
It was used in the original equipment itself.
Oh, this?
Yes, it is.
Oh, isn't this good?
Then it's the real thing.
Then I'll ask you to put it down in the middle.
Now that I have been appointed to this position, I will do my best until next year,
I will do my best until next year to make it all happen.
Let's have fun together. I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much. So, we now have the opening, Theory.
And the chief ambassador for the ladies of Wartrace Hamanaka is finished.
I was nervous.
I was so nervous. It was a little too hot today, about 36 degrees forecast.
I was sweating a lot.
But everyone was so kind to watch over me.
And last time, I collaborated with Momoe Shibata in the collaborative boat race club.
I was so happy to be able to give Momoe-chan flowers.
I was so happy to be able to hand over the flowers to Momoe-chan, and I was also very excited to see Eri Miura, who was the other winner of the race, which was an extraordinary event.
Well, we were able to finish the day well, so all I have to do now is to make the day more exciting.
I will do my best. The panels are going to be great, so please come visit us at the Boat Race Hamanaka.